like say welcome brothers and sisters to
another Wednesday question and answer
will we open up with the Ten
Commandments that God commanded the
whole world to keep brother James yes
sir and God spake all these words saying
I am the Lord thy God which have brought
thee out of the land of Egypt out of the
house of bondage Thou shalt have no
other gods before me thou shall not make
unto thee any Graven image or any
likeness of anything that is in heaven
above or that is in the earth beneath or
that is in the water under the Earth
Thou shalt not bow down thyself to them
nor serve them for I the Lord thy God am
a jealous God visiting the iniquity of
the fathers upon the children unto the
third and fourth generation of them that
hate me and showing Mercy unto thousands
of them that love me and keep my
Commandments Thou shalt not take the
name of the Lord thy God God in vain for
the Lord will not hold him Guiltless
that taketh his name in vain remember
the Sabbath day to keep it holy six days
shalt thou labor and do all thy work but
the seventh day is the Sabbath of the
Lord thy God Thou shalt not do any work
thou nor thy son nor thy daughter thy
manservant nor thy maid servant nor thy
cattle nor thy stranger that is within
thy gates for in six days the Lord made
Heaven and Earth the sea and all that in
them is and rested the seventh day
wherefore the Lord blessed the Sabbath
day and hollowed it honor thy father and
thy mother that thy days may be long
upon the land which the Lord thy God
giveth thee Thou shalt not kill Thou
shalt not commit adultery Thou shalt not
steal Thou shalt not bear false witness
against thy neighbor Thou shalt not
cover thy neighbor's house Thou shalt
not cover thy neighbor's wife nor his
man's servant nor his maid servant nor
his Ox nor his ass nor anything that is
thy neighbors I read Exodus 20 veres
1-17 may the Lord add a blessing to the
reading of this word in Jesus name we
pray amen
amen so here on question and answer you
can ask us a question and we'll answer
it according to the King James Bible and
if we cannot find the answer we will
seek further counsel to bring you an
answer at a later time the questions we
will not answer are the vague questions
and the long scripture questions and the
questions of debate we are not here to
debate we are here to spread the gospel
of the true and living God so please be
as direct as possible with your
questions so we can be as direct as
possible with our answers out of the
King James Bible no other Bibles will be
acknowledged on this program that also
applies to books that don't pertain to
the King James Bible also keep in mind
that this is a live stream so feel free
to send in your questions that pertain
to everlasting life we just ask that you
keep your questions to a two scripture
maximum let me introduce to you the
family that's on the panel this evening
we got brother Dre good evening brother
Jerome Grace and peace Brother Julius
good evening everybody brother James
good evening everyone sister Deborah
good evening brother
Sean good evening and we have the guest
caller with us and I'm brother Cornell
sister Deborah what is our first
question of the evening yes there are
several held over questions that will be
answered first before getting into
tonight's Q&A uh so Stephen gugus asss
who was the servant of the high priest
that was smitten and ear was cut in Mark
14 verse
47 all right who was that servant of the
high priest that was smitten and his ear
was cut in Mark 14 and 47 brother
Julius who was that let's go there
brother James let's go answer this
question yes
sir Mark 14 and verse 47 and then we're
gonna go one other place go
ahead and one of them that stood by Drew
a sword and smote a servant of the high
priest and cut off his ear now so what
we got uh we got uh let's name two
people here let's go to St John the 18th
chapter St John the 18 chapter we going
to get a name of the person that Drew
The Sword and we're going to get a name
of the person whose ear is cut
off St John 18th chapter and let's pick
it up at verse
three Judas then having received a band
of men and officers from the chief
priests and Pharisees cometh thither
with lanterns and torches and weapons
uhhuh Jesus therefore knowing all things
that should come upon him went forth and
said unto them whom seek ye yes they
answered him Jesus of Nazareth Jesus
said unto them I am he and Judas also
which betrayed him stood with him so now
let's go skip all the way down to verse
10 and go ahead then Simon Peter having
a sword drew it and and smote the high
priest's servant and cut off his right
ear the servant's name was maliss so now
that's why you don't need to interpret
you just need to continue to read here a
little and there a little and you'll get
the whole story so it was the Jesus
disciple Peter who drew the sword and
cut off malus's ear so we got Peter and
we got the servant whose ear would cut
off was of the high priest was malcus I
hope that
helped yes sir brother Jud listen we
know the power came Jesus also healed
that same ear that was cut off didn't he
you can read that part in Matthew the
26th chapter at verse 51 it would tell
you later on in the chapter that he put
picked his ear up told Peter to put his
sword back in his sheath and he he put
the ear back on and healed the and
healed the man healed the malus's
ear yes sir out of the mouth of two or
more witnesses is a fact
established yes that was a power there
all right we hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next one
okay next one he also ask what is the
meaning of this scripture from Micah 7
verse5 Micah 7 verse five Dre what you
say let's go to that Micah 7 and let's
pick it up at verse two and read verses
two and three and we'll skip to five
from that okay go ahead and read it when
you get it J the good man has perished
out of the earth and there is none
upright among men they all lie and wait
for blood they hunt every man his
brother with a net that they may do evil
with both hands earnestly The Prince
askes and the judge
askthe he utth his Mis mischievous
desire so they wrap it up so every body
is corrupt here skip down to verse five
go ahead trust ye not in a friend put ye
not confidence in a God keep the doors
of thy mouth from her that lith in thy
bosom in other words he telling them hey
your friend can turn on you the person
that's guiding you he can mislead you
the the woman that's sleeping in your
bosom May
hurt
you if you telling her everything let's
go to Matthew the 10th chapter and look
at one one other place Matthew 10 and
pick it up at verse 34 Matthew 10 and
34 think not that I am come to send
peace on Earth I came not to send peace
but a
sword for I come to set a man at
variance against his father and the
daughter against her mother and the
daughter-in-law against her
mother-in-law and a man's fold shall be
they of his own household so when you
carrying that sword which is the word of
God that sword is a sword of separation
and it can divide folks that's not right
with you and and you know at the end of
the day that word of God either you deal
with it are you not but keep reading
read a little bit more of that go ahead
he that loveth father or mother more
than me is not worthy of me and he that
loveth son or daughter more than me is
not worthy of me uhhuh and he that
taketh not his cross and followeth after
me is not worthy of me one last verse go
ahead he that findeth his life shall
lose Lo it and he that loseth his life
for my sake shall find it so stay with
the word no matter what you dealing with
and Micah Micah was looking at it and
nothing has changed because each
generation folks GNA deal with this if
you in the word you gonna have to stand
in the word and sometimes your own worst
enemies may be they of your own
household it is right gotta stand on the
word
y that's all I got yes sir all right
hope that ansed your question as we
continue to move on to our next question
moving on Joanne Durham says my husband
has filed for divorce if I sign the
settlement agreement is that going
against God's word so the husband is
filed for divorce and the wife want to
know that if she signed a settlement
agreement is that going against God's
word guest
caller and the first thing first first
thing is what do you call a settlement
agreement look like there's more
involved in there just signing for a
divorce so I think the question need to
be
redirected because what do you call the
settlement
agreement sound like a business deal to
me that's all I have to say all
right hope that
um shine some light on you as uh you
resubmit the question if you so feel the
need all right moving on to our next
question next question sweet te M High
says I was told by a Hebrew brother that
following Jesus is following a pagan
deity what verse and chapter can I take
him to that
explain Jesus is the high
priest all right brother Jerome this
question is in definite need of some
light well first I'd like to address the
the uh Hebrew brother saying that uh
Jesus is a pagan deity okay he is not
okay so let's go to uh Matthews the 1
chapter verse 23 and I'mma tie that with
uh Isaiah the 9th
chapter
okay you get it go ahead and read Behold
a virgin shall be with child and shall
bring forth a son and they shall call
his name Emmanuel which being
interpreted is God With Us okay I'm a
Believer so if the if the word of God
say God With Us I'm of the faith to
believe that okay and so let's tie that
with the Isaiah chapter 9 verse
6 For unto us a child is born unto us a
son is given and the government shall be
upon his shoulder and his name Shall be
Called wonderful counselor the Mighty
God the Everlasting father the Prince of
Peace it call him the Mighty
God okay the Everlasting father he not
our father but he he's not the father
let me get that correct he not the
father but he our father because he
adopted us and made us his children okay
but it call him the Mighty God right
there the child that was born the same
one we just read in Matthews the first
chapter okay now the second um part of
this question was
explaining uh how Jesus is the high
priest let's go to Hebrews the 7th
chapter before you go further you should
read Isaiah the 7th chapter about the
version
okay because that's what Matthew's first
chapter
explain all
right that's around at verse uh
14 okay verse 14 Isaiah 7 ver14 says
therefore the Lord himself shall give
you a sign Behold a virgin shall
conceive and bear a son and shall call
his name
Emmanuel thank you
gu know and Emmanuel mean God Is With Us
yeah yeah that's why Matthew said he
call his name Emmanuel God was with us
said God God himself they'll give you a
sign he didn't send an angel he came
himself okay that's
all now let's deal with thank you guest
caller now let's go to the uh the high
priest part of this question to show
that Jesus uh is the high priest after
the order of MEC so let's go to Hebrews
the 7th
chapter and pick it up at 15 Read to the
17 okay
and it is yet far more evident for that
after the similitude of mized there
arises another priest who is made not
after the law of a carnal commandment
but after the power of an endless life
for he testifieth thou art a priest
Forever After the order of
mesc and now let's skip to the sixth
chapter and read verse 20 establish
that's
Jesus when you get go ahead and read
whether the Forerunner is for us entered
even Jesus made an high priest for Ever
After the order of Mel eedc yeah that's
all I
got all right yes sir hope that
answerers your question as we move on to
our next question our next question she
also asks when a person speaks against
the kjb holy
word where can I show them its
blasphemy they speak against the KJV
holy word where can they show his
blasphemy guest
caller ain't nowhere they can show it
you know why because if they going to
speak against the Bible how you going to
go into the Bible and prove a point to
them that be a waste of your
time is right
all right hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next one
moving on Paula sanfer
said my sister continued to operate in
sexual
immortality and smoking weed even after
getting baptized she has
realized
immorality immorality thank you my
sister continued to operate in sexual
immorality and smoking weed even after
getting
baptized she has realized her error and
stopped She has
repented will the Lord forgive
her well um all things are possible with
God as long as you you living um but
some of the things you have to do when
you take a fall like this I don't know
where she was baptized at but if she was
baptized with us then we know that um
she knows that some of these things that
she was doing was not right but as far
as smoking weed hey whosoever committed
sin transgress of also the law for sin
is the transgression of the law might
not be good for you but can't read where
it say thou shall not smoke that but
some places will take your job so be
very careful with that but let's go into
um that uh Matthew the thir chapter
Matthew 3 because you said that uh if
she is
repented there's someone higher than us
all who needs to definitely see that the
repentance has taken
place let's read that Matthew
3 and let's pick it up at that verse
eight and then we go skip down go ahead
bring forth their so you're I'm sorry
bring forth therefore fruits meat for
repentance so that is the main thing
before the Lord we want always show that
we sorry for the sins that we committed
and then we don't do those no more skip
down to verse 10 because we have to be
careful that we don't fall back into the
ways of the world go ahead and now also
the axes laid unto the root of the trees
therefore every tree which bringeth
forth bringeth not forth good fruit is
heed down and cast into the fire so you
have to fight these things that's
against God because he is watching all
of us turn over to Ezekiel 18 Ezekiel
the 18th
chapter
okay because every day you got to get up
and fight put on that whole arm of God
so you can do the things that please the
Lord Ezekiel 18 pick it up at that verse
26 go ahead
when a righteous man turneth away from
his righteousness and committeth
iniquity and and dieth in them for his
iniquity that he ha done shall he die
and that is a key word when they dieth
in them that's why we can't go back to
the world and participate in that
because you don't want that to be your
last act doing Wicked before the Lord
27 again when the Wicked Man turneth
away from his Wicked
that he hath committed and doeth that
which is lawful and right he shall save
his soul alive so if you truly repented
then you do the things which are lawful
and right so that you can save your soul
alive
28 because he
considerthe from all his transgressions
that he hath committed he shall surely
live he shall not die that's the
responsibility of everybody skip down to
that verse uh 30 that'll be it go ahead
therefore I will judge you oh House of
Israel everyone according to his ways
sayeth the Lord God repent and turn
yourselves from all your transgressions
so iniquity shall not be your ruin so we
know that the Lord is merciful and
therefore sure she's truly repentant you
know the Lord can for G but you have to
make sure that you're doing this thing
with all your might and fight the evil
that so easily takes us over that's all
I
got all right we hope that yes caller go
right here Solomon spoke of of a
uh when he said long as you living
there's hope there's any Ecclesiastes
think the nth chapter nth
chapter and when don't read get there
and read
it all right 9 and
four okay for to him that is joined to
all the living there is hope for a
living dog is better than a dead
line now but go ahead but there living
dog is better than a dead
line but it's more to it than
that so no that's all as long as you to
him that's join to the living there is
hope so as long as you are
living there's hope all you got to do is
repent like brother Cornell
said okay yep all right thank you for
that add on we hope that answered your
question there as we move on to our next
question moving on
AHS is the Holy Ghost only Gabriel
or can there be more than one Holy Ghost
given that angels are ministering
Spirits all right it's the Holy Ghost
only Gabriel Brother
Julius let's go and let's look at the
Holy Ghost it it depends upon the term
or the context of which is written Let's
Go and show you what is also holy and
what is also Spirit God is a spirit in
John 4 and 24 but James let's go to um
joh St John 6 and 63 first let's move
quick through this St John 6 and read
verse
63 it is the spirit that quickeneth the
flesh profiteth nothing the words that I
speak unto you they are spirit and they
are life so the word of God is spirit is
spiritual okay the word of God is spirit
and it is life now let's go to Hebrews
chapter one mhm M Hebrews chapter
1 and pick this up at verse 7 and we
from we'll read seven and verses 14 for
the sake of time go ahead and of the
angels He saith who maketh his Angel
spirits and his ministers a flame of
fire so angels are Spirit whether they
are holy or whether they're Unholy the
Unholy are evil spirits are fallen
angels and the holy ones are righteous
Angels okay now verse 14 are they not
all ministering Spirits sent forth to
minister for them who shall be HS of
Salvation now I want you to highlight
sisters and brothers sent forth
ministering spirits that are they all
ministering Spirits sent forth they are
they don't go on their own they are sent
they are sent sisters and brothers Luke
1 Luke
1 and I want you to read verse 26 Luke 1
and verse
26 and in the sixth month the angel
Gabriel was sent from God unto a city of
Galilee named Nazareth now we have a
named Angel here Gabriel and he is sent
remember they're all sent from god so
let's go to Daniel the 8th
chapter Daniel chapter
8 and I want I want you to read verses
15 and
16 Daniel 815 because Daniel had a
vision the lord gave him a vision and he
didn't understand let's see who was sent
to him Daniel 8 and 15 go ahead and it
came to pass when I even I Daniel had
seen the vision and sought for the
meaning then behold there stood before
me as the appearance of a man and I
heard a man's voice between the bank of
Eli which called and said Gabriel make
this man to understand the vision so now
Gabriel is sent to Daniel just like he
was sent to Mary it calls him a man but
we know that he is an angel let's go to
Isaiah
63 the book of Isaiah
63 and we gonna pick this up brother
James we gon to read verses eight and
nine pay attention to what we're reading
here go ahead for he said surely they
are my people children that will not lie
so he was their savior in all their
Affliction he was afflicted and the
angel of his presence saved them in his
love his what of his presence the angel
of his presence saved them go ahead in
his love and in his peity he redeemed
them and he bare them and carried them
all the days of oath
Luke chapter 1 and I got one place after
this Luke chapter
1 Luke chapter 1 my brother and we're G
to read verse
19 Luke chapter 1
19 and when you get that read it and the
angel answering said unto him I am to
zaras and Elizabeth and zachar Zacharias
the angel was sent to them to announce
to them the birth of John the Baptist
and look what he start at the top of
that brother go ahead and the angel
answering said unto him I am Gabriel
that stand in the presence of God and am
sent to speak unto thee and to show thee
things Glad Tidings so now he said I am
Gabriel so we got the name of an angel
or a Holy Spirit and he said I am sent
to show unto you like we don't read two
other places where he is sent all right
now my last place let's go to Revelation
the 22nd
chapter cuz all the Angels serve God but
he got one that stands in his presence
revelation
22 and when you get there brother read
verse 16 and we'll be
done I Jesus have sent mine Angel to
testify unto you these things in the
churches so now he said I Jesus have
sent my my angel that's one presence he
didn't say angels He said and my
angel to testify to you things in the
churches go ahead I am the root and The
Offspring of David and the bright and
Morning Star that's all I
got that's all I got brother Cornell
anybody else want to comment on
that all right hope that answered your
question we're going to keep it moving
yes moving on Jennifer Love
says uh if a person is not baptized
before Jesus return will they be
baptized in the
wilderness if a person is not baptized
before Jesus returns will they be
baptized in the wilderness guess
caller well you have to get baptized if
you going to get salvation that's right
but the whole the whole thing is a
person don't believe enough to get
baptized he not going to believe enough
to flee to the Wilderness when it's time
to
come it's all that simple so most
[Music]
likely it's all about your faith if you
don't have faith enough in the Lord to
get baptized then what make you think
you're going to have you're going to
believe it when you see the sign to go
to the Wilderness you're not going to
believe that either
most likely he'll never get to the
Wilderness that's all I have to
say yeah keep in mind Jesus himself was
baptized so goes the world
here all right hope that answered your
question as we move on moving on She
also asked if there will be no more
death after Jesus return am I misreading
Ezekiel 47
verse2 and Isaiah 65
verse2 all right brother
Jerome let's go read those verses given
in the question uh Ezekiel
47-12 you get it go ahead and read and
by the river upon the bank thereof on
this side and on that side shall grow
all trees for meat whose Leaf shall not
fade neither shall the fruit thereof be
consumed it shall bring forth new fruit
according to his months because their
Waters they issued out of the sanctuary
and the fruit thereof shall be for meat
and the leaf thereof for
medicine yeah so that's that's that's
kind of dealing with the um Lord's
Kingdom and this Kingdom going to be
4,000 years let's go look at the other
verse Isaiah 65 and
20 there shall be no more then an infant
of days nor an old man that have not
filled his days for the child shall die
100 years old but the sinner being 100
years old shall be a
cursed yeah so right there in the verse
let you
know um doing the Lord's Um Kingdom why
he here for a thousand years it's still
going to be people dying all right in
his kingdom okay but after his thousand
years is is
accomplished uh you go go you going to
go right into the father's Kingdom and
it ain't going to be no death in his
kingdom okay so now let's go to um 1
Corinthians chapter 15
and we're going to read verse 24-
26 okay then cometh the end when he
shall have delivered up the kingdom to
God even the father when he shall have
put down all Rule and all authority and
power for he must Reign till he have put
all enemies under his feet The Last
Enemy that shall be destroyed is
death yeah
so that's the Last Enemy he going to
destroy and he going to destroy that
within that Thousand-Year um period that
he G to reain for you know like we like
you read in Revelations 20 so let's go
there Revelations
20 okay and pick it up at the
13 and the and the Sea gave up the Dead
which were in it and death and Hell
delivered up the dead which were in them
and they were judged every man according
to their
works so this goingon to happen uh you
know before that thousand year reign of
Christ is over
with because all this got to be taken
care of in in time Manan he going to
Reign which is 4,000 years okay and then
you going to go into the father's
Kingdom uh but read that 14
and death and hell were cast into the
Lake of Fire this is the second death
all right remember that Last Enemy he
was supposed to take care of was death
all right now he he going he took care
within that Thousand Years span so now
we going into the father's King and go
right into Revelations 21 and read verse
1-4 and that'll be it and I saw a new
Heaven and a new Earth for the first
Heaven and the first Earth were passed
away and there was no more SE
and I John saw the holy city New
Jerusalem coming down from God out of
Heaven prepared as a bride adorned for
her husband and I heard a great voice
out of Heaven saying behold the
Tabernacle of God is with men and he
will dwell with them and they shall be
his people and God himself shall be with
them and be their God and God shall wipe
away all tears from their eyes and there
shall be no more death neither sorrow
nor crying neither shall there be any
more pain for the former things are
passed
away that's all I
got all right thank you for that brother
hope that answered that question as we
move on to our next next one most love
as in Ezra 9 verse2
is that a law and if so does it still
stand in Ezra 9 and 12 is that a law or
does it still stand when you get
there brother James want you to read
that got 1 Chronicles 2 Chronicles and
Ezra 9 and verse 12 and the guest caller
would take it from
there now therefore give Not Your
Daughters unto their sons neither take
their daughters unto your sons nor seek
their peace or their wealth forever that
ye may be strong and eat the good of the
land and leave it for an inheritance to
your children
forever okay now this was talking at
that particular time that was talking
about the
Canaanites but then that sply about the
Canaanites but there is the LA where the
Lord told Israel not to marry uh outside
the nation and Solomon proved that that
the Lord was talking about more than the
Canaanite but in this particular place
it was talking about the Canaanites but
let's go quickly to first king the 11th
chapter and see what God said about
other people first king 11 read verses 1
and
two first king 11 verse 1 and two says
but King Solomon loved many strange
women together with the daughter of
pharaoh women of the moabites ammonites
zonian ites and the Hittites of
the Nations concerning which the Lord
said unto the children of Israel ye
shall not go into them neither shall
they come in unto you for surely they
will turn away your heart after their
gods Solomon clay unto these in
love now they only name one in there
that was from among the Canaanites and
there were the
Hittites but the amorites moabites those
are lot lot's
children and the Egyptians so they are
still stranger and the Lord said these
are these are people that the Lord said
I should not
marry but then
Moses married in
Ethiopia and when miam and uh uh Aaron
started to uh uh talk against them the
Lord turned Miriam
white yep then again uh David's
grandmother is a
moabit so spoke about other people but
this particular place in Ezra 9 was
talking strictly about the
Canaanites and who are the Canaanites
now they were scattered the ones that
wasn't killed and now Israel is
scattered so that particular thing about
the Canaanite cannot be enforced tonight
now cannot uh uh uh uh be going on right
now but because who are the
canit that's all I have to say all right
hope that answered your question as we
move on with the time check to our next
one yes the time is
8:09 and cash in
8888 says in Revelation 5:
5-9 it talks about Jesus taking the book
from the father did they see the father
was that a vision into the future when
the father came
down all right brother
Julius let's go to that scripture and
read
that okay
and let's answer this question according
to what's written remember the whole
book of Revelation is a
vision Revelation 5 and pick it up at
verse
five and one of the elders saith unto me
weep not Behold The Lion of the tribe of
Judah the root of David have prevailed
to open the book and to loose the Seven
Seals
thereof and I behad H and low in the
midst of the throne and of the four
beasts and in the midst of the elders
stood a lamb as it as it had been slain
having seven horns and seven eyes which
are the seven spirits of God sent forth
into all the Earth and he came and took
the book out of the right hand of him
that sat upon the throne and when he
telling you what happened didn't say it
saw his face did
continue to read and when he had taken
the book The Four beasts and 4 and 20
Elders fell down before the lamb having
every one of them Harps and golden vials
full of oders which are the prayers of
saints uhuh and they sung a new song
saying Thou Art Worthy to the to take
the book and to open the seals thereof
for thou was slain and has redeemed us
to God by thy blood out of every Kindred
and tongue and people and Nation now
let's go to St John the first
chapter John is telling you what he saw
he just said Jesus Took the book out of
the hand of him that sit on the throne
John 1:18 and that's all I
got no man has seen God at any time the
only begotten son which is in the bosom
of the father he had declared him he had
declared him so now we can show you
that Moses
ABAB naab and 20 uh four the elders saw
the god of Israel but they didn't see
the father they didn't see the father
they saw Jesus because we've always only
dealt with Jesus this is a vision and
this is yet to come but hey it's telling
you about what he saw that's all I
got read John
537 than John 5 and 37 that is right
thank
you St John 5 and 37 yes sir the father
himself which has sent me have borne
witness of me ye have neither heard his
voice at any time nor seen his shape
that is Kitty lock the door right there
that's it
you have neither seen the father his
shape or heard his voice at any time
that's all I got Cornel thank you guest
call all right hope that answered your
question as we continue to move on
moving on uh kly ask ass is it okay to
watch nature shows on the Sabbath for
example Animal
Planet uh no it's not okay to watch
nature shows on the Sabbath because you
can watch those for six days a week and
I also enjoy some of those animal shows
but not on the Sabbath day because this
is a holy day and when you treat it holy
then you have certain things that you do
for that day and things that you can do
the other six days but let's go to
Isaiah 58 because that's a that's a
pleasure watching animal shows you can
sit back and kick your feet up and get
lost in it for I was on in I know
because I've done it before but not on
the Sabbath day Isaiah
58 and let's see about this this sabbath
day
here verse 13 go ahead if thou turn away
thy foot from the Sabbath from doing thy
pleasure on my holy day and call the
Sabbath a delight the holy of the Lord
honorable and shalt honor him not doing
thine own ways nor finding thine own
pleasure nor speaking thine own words so
if you don't find your own Pleasures not
even supposed to be speaking your own
words but that is a way that you treat
the Sabbath day because it is indeed
holy and it's honorable and Jesus
himself say that he rested on that day
so we must respect him to the fullest
verse
14 then shalt thou Delight thyself in
the Lord and I will cause thee to ride
upon the high places of the earth and
feed thee with the heritage of Jacob thy
father for the mouth of the Lord has
spoken it so the answer to that is no
you have to watch that for six days but
on the seventh day no Animal Planet and
no nature shows or things of that nature
and that's all I
got and thank you hope that answered
your question as we move on to our next
moving on to the next one Renee Israel
says the ones that are blessed to flee
to the Wilderness in Revelation 12
verse6 and then in
quotation uh she has the woman will they
be helping Jesus teach in the wilderness
in Ezekiel
20: 33-39
and Isaiah 16
verse1 all right
so let's go to that Revelation 12 and6
the woman where they be helping Jesus
teach in the wilderness but we're going
to turn this over to the Gest
called okay Revelation 12 and6 says and
the woman fled Into the Wilderness where
she hath a place prepared of God that
they should feed her there
1,23 score
days okay read Ezekiel
203 3
to39
Ezekiel 20 20
33 33-39 says as I live sayth the Lord
God surely a mighty hand with a
stretched out arm and with Fury pour out
will I rule over you and I will bring
you out from the people and will gather
you out of the countries wherein ye are
scattered with a mighty hand and with a
stretched out arm and with Fury poured
out and I will bring you into the
Wilderness of the people and there will
I plead with you face to face like as I
pleaded with your fathers in the
wilderness out of the land of Egypt so
will I plead with you sayeth the Lord
God
and I will cause you to pass under the
rod and I will bring you into the bond
of the Covenant and I will Purge out
from among you the rebels and them that
transgress against me I will bring them
forth out of the country where they
sourn and they shall not enter into the
land of Israel and ye shall have known
that I am the Lord as for you
oh now let go Isaiah 16 and read verse
one okay Isaiah 16:1 says send ye the
lamb to the ruler of the land from Salah
to the Wilderness unto the Mount of the
daughter of
Zion now this is why the question was
asked that women going to teach in the
wilderness the answer is no they send
you the lamb to the daughter of Zion is
not talking about sending the lamb to a
woman the daughters of is talking about
Israel first thing here we going to pay
attention what we start this thing out
with now let's go back to 12 uh uh
Revelation the 12th chapter and read 1
and two first revelation 12 1
and2 Revelation
12 one and two then down and read and
six okay verse 1 and two says and there
appeared a great Wonder in
a woman clothed with the sun and the
moon under her feet and upon her head a
crown of 12 stars and she being being
with child cried travailing in birth and
pain to be
delivered verse
five and she brought forth a Manchild
who was to rule all nations with the rod
of iron and her child was caught up unto
God and to his throne and the woman fled
Into the Wilderness where she ha a place
prepared of God that they should feed
her there
1,23 score
days now this woman is not talking about
a
female just like the Don design is not
talking about uh female it's talking
about all Israel so let's go and show
you that this is talking about all
Israel go to Genesis the 37th chapter
read verse one and two first okay
Genesis 37 verse1 and2 says and Jacob
dwelt in the land wherein his father was
a stranger in the land of Canaan these
are the generations of Jacob Joseph
being 17 years old was feeding the flock
with his Brethren and the lad was with
the sons of BHA and with the sons of
Zila his father's wives and Joseph
brought unto his father their evil
report I skip down to verse
five and Joseph dreamed a dream and he
told it told it his Brethren and they
hated him yet the
more now skip down to verse n he had
another dream go ahead and he dreamed
yet another dream and told it to his
Brethren and said behold I have dreamed
a dream more and behold the Son and the
moon and the 11 stars made obes to
me now keep reading oh and he told it to
his father and to his Brethren and and
his father rebuked him and said unto him
what is this dream that thou has dreamed
shall I and thy mother and thy Brethren
indeed come to bow down ourselves to
thee to the
earth now and
his that
woman was uh uh uh talking about Israel
go back and read verse one again
Revelation 1 12 And1 rather go back and
read Revelation 12 And1 okay Revelation
12:1
says and there appeared a great Wonder
in heaven a woman clothed with the sun
and the moon under her feet and upon her
head a
go with the son the son represent Jacob
that's why he say shall I and Y my and
your mother because the Moon represent
the
mother
and how many stars did she have in her
head a crown of 12
stars that represent the 12 tribes of
Israel so this woman which fled and the
daughter of Zion is not talking about a
woman it's talking about all
Israel so no going to be no woman
teaching in the
wilderness that's that's all I have to
say all right hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next one
moving on Malik Shakur
says in Isaiah 3 verse1 17 is that the
reason why most black women hair is hard
to grow
uh brother Dre what you
say let's go to Isaiah 3 and let's pick
it up at verse 16
Isaiah moreover the Lord saith because
the daughters of Zion are halty and walk
with stretched forth necks and wanting
eyes walking and mincing as they go and
making a tinkling with their feet go
ahead therefore for the Lord will Smite
with a scab the crown of the head of the
daughters of Zion and the Lord will
discover their secret Parts go
ahead in that day the Lord will take
away The Bravery of their tinkling
ornaments about their feet and their
calls and their round tires like the
moon notice it said in that day right go
ahead read a little more the chains and
the bracelets and the m lers the Bonnets
and the ornaments of the legs and the
headbands and the tablets and the
earrings the Rings and the nose Jewels
the changeable suits of apparel and the
mantels and The Wimp wimples And The
crisping pin now you see all that right
now today but you can't associate with a
woman hair not growing because a lot of
women got well said hair right now skip
down to verse 24 go ahead and it shall
come to pass that instead of sweet smell
of I'm sorry it shall come to pass that
instead of sweet smell there shall be
stink and instead of a girdle a rent and
instead of well set hair baldness and
instead of a stomacher a giring of
sackcloth and burning instead of beauty
go ahead thy men shall fall By The Sword
and thy Mighty in the war so this is
going to happen in in the sense that
people are going through mourning
because they in war and death is coming
and if you read the fourth chapter and
the fir go to the fourth chapter and
read the first verse there
okay and in that day seven women shall
take hold of one man saying we will eat
of our own bread and wear our own
apparel only let us be called by thy
name to take away our reproach in that
day that day ain't here right now women
got well set hair they got better jobs
than men do no that's not talking about
that okay that's that's
it all right yes sir Dre we we are
created them afro didn't we back in the
day that's right some of these sisters
got them sister locks and they hair is
flourishing they don't put in there
their hair is growing really
good
yeah like you said in that day the day
to come brother yes sir all right thank
you for that hope that answer that
question sister Deborah we going into
new
territory yes we are
we are now into tonight's Q&A for
December the 18
2024 first question why can't I
celebrate
Christmas why can't I celebrate
Christmas majority of the world is going
to be celebrating it brother Julius so
share some light on why can't I
celebrate Christmas uh because God said
don't do it Christmas is a season the
December the 25th is a day within the
season okay it is celebrated it is Pagan
from beginning to the middle to the end
of it it is Pagan Pagan Pagan and in the
winter time they call it the winter
solstice and it is named after the Roman
god soul in celebration and it was
celebrated way before Jesus came on the
scene the pagans celebrated this stuff
sisters and brothers so therefore you
can't put God where he don't put himself
God said not to do it let's go to
Deuteronomy the 12th chapter James
Deuteronomy chapter 12
okay Pagan Pagan Pagan you know right
there don't fly ain't nobody gonna come
put chimney down to it down your chimney
it is all mythology and paganism
Deuteronomy 12:29 let's
go 12 and 29 says when the Lord thy God
shall cut off the nations from before
thee whether thou goest to possess them
and thou succeed them and dwelleth in
their land uhhuh take heed to thyself
that that thou be not snared by
following them after don't do the things
that the people of the land did that the
Lord cast out go ahead after that they
be destroyed from before thee and that
thou inquire not after their God saying
how did these Nation Nations serve their
gods even so will I do likewise the Lord
don't want you to do that go ahead Thou
shalt not do so unto the Lord thy God
right for every Abomination to the Lord
which he hateth have they done unto
their gods for even their sons and their
daughters they have burnt in the fire to
their gods and we sacrifice our children
to moak and all that kind of stuff give
me verse 32 what should we do what
things soever I command You observe to
do it Thou shalt not add th to nor
diminish from it don't do what the Lord
say do if you love him You Gonna Keep
His Commandments why John 4 St John 4
and
24 God is everything that the Lord said
don't
do John 4 and verse 24 James just verse
24 read it God is a spirit and they that
worship him must worship Him in spirit
and in truth now let's look at what we
do on this H H uh coming up to this day
I mean it's all Pagan St John the 10th
chapter St John chapter I'm sorry
Jeremiah chapter 10 okay Jeremiah
chapter 10 because there are only two
birthdays that are celebrated that we
read in the Bible and that is Pharaoh
that's in Genesis chapter 40 and in
Herod in uh Matthew the 14th chapter and
both of those days are celebrated now if
the Lord wanted us to celebrate his
birth he surely he would have had it
written surely he would have had it
written Jeremiah 10 and verse one
Jeremiah 10 verse one go ahead brother
hear ye the word which the Lord speaketh
unto you oh House of Israel yes thus
sayth the Lord learn not the way of the
Heathen and be not dismayed at the signs
of heaven so now on that tree you got
all your ornaments on that representing
the planets you got the Little Star on
on the top of that also a host of heaven
star Sun stars and moon everything is
Pagan from the uog to the mlto you know
what they actually did the pagans did on
misto they had sex
ories that's why people kiss each other
on there because that's how they
initiated the mistl toe and it really
gets more gross than that when you do
the extensive research of it it is not
biblical continue to read James for the
Heathen are dismayed at them for the
customs of the people are vain uhhuh for
one cutteth a tree out of the forest the
work of the hands of the workmen with
the axe now you got the tree already
preut and you go to the store or to the
Christmas tree lot buy tie down on your
on your huh go ahead they deck it with
silver and with gold deck it means
decorate they decorated with Sil that's
the little tsils that you put on it and
the gold and the silver then you bow
down to it and put the Prejudice
underneath it and then you sing songs
and whole hands oh Christmas tree oh
Christmas tree Pagan Pagan Pagan go
ahead they fasten it with nails and with
hammers that it move not now you put it
in a stand and you screw it in go ahead
they are upright as the palm tree but
speak not they must needs be born
because they cannot go because you have
to carry it you got to carry it into
your on top of your car you got to carry
it into the house it can't walk there's
nothing wrong with the tree the tree
nothing wrong with it it's the creation
of God but continue to finish it up be
not afraid of them for they cannot do
evil neither also is it is it in them to
do good it is not the tree it is the
worship of it and what it's associated
with give me verse eight and that'll be
it but they are Al together brutish and
foolish the stock is a doctrine of
vanities the whole Christmas season from
the tree to everything associated with
it the U TI the U all of it it's Pagan
sisters and brothers that's why the Lord
said come out of her my people my people
are destroyed lack of knowledge that's
all I got you so you're saying Julius
with Christmas no and with bringing a
tree into your home no you shouldn't do
this ask yourselves sisters and brothers
why are you carrying a tree into your
house where in the Bible did the Lord
tell you to celebrate his birth date it
is not written but we can read a whole
lot of pagan gods that was born December
the 25th including tamuz and Apollos and
Helios and all and so on and so forth
and the gods of Egypt Pagan Pagan Pagan
I like what the books say if you love me
keep my Commandments and do the things
that I say
do he said remember his birth I remember
his resurrection they got that wrong
they celebrating that wrong cuz they
call it
Easter and you can't get three days and
three nights that's another lesson of
the
time yes sir when a person ask a simple
question you give them a simple answer
Jeremiah the 10th chapter was the answer
to that question thank you sometime
overt okay yes
sir all right hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next
question uh next question uh Gordon
Scott have two questions uh one when God
told David he could not build him a
house because too much blood was on his
hands in 1 Chronicles
22:8 was this from war or from basheba
because he said Wars and two is was the
coast of skins the Lord God Made For
Adam and Eve from a
lamb right look like we got two
questions here Jerome what you say let's
go read that first chonicles 22 and8
okay I'm
there but the word but the word of the
Lord came to me saying thou has shed
blood abundantly and has made great Wars
Thou shalt not build an house unto my
name because thou has shed much blood
upon the Earth in my sight
yeah because of the many wars that's
what it is it ain't because of B Sheba
it's because of the many wars he shed
much blood which God uh had him to do
you know but he didn't want the Lord he
didn't want him to build his house
because of that okay because of the wars
now the second
question uh the cult to skin in Genesis
it really don't say it was a lamb so I
can't say it's a lamb and um I can
remember reading about John the Baptist
he had uh um camel's hair that he wore
and you know camel's hair camel actually
is not a clean animal you know
but that's all I got on that anybody
else want to add
something yeah just just to back up what
you said uh Jerome let's go to Genesis 3
and just read that
and we won't like you say we won't get
the word uh lamb out of there Genesis
3 and pick it up at that U verse
20 well 19 just read down into it 19
because this is after Adam and Eve and
did their sin in here go ahead in the
sweat of thy face shalt thou eat bread
till thou return unto the ground for out
of it was thou taken for dust thou AR
and unto dust shalt thou
return and Adam called his wife his
wife's name Eve because she was the
mother of all living one more unto Adam
also and to his wife did the Lord make
coats of skins and clothe them all right
so like you say brother Jerome we we
can't see no lamb there right we just
see coats of skin
yeah yeah okay all right right thank you
for that brother hope that answer that
question as we move on moving on June
green says I'm
going I'm about to go abroad I intend to
listen to the class from
iog in my hotel room but before and
after that am I allowed to still
meditate on God but be in the sun Maybe
be relaxing on the beach or do I have to
stay in my room the whole duration of
Sabbath all right well we know you're
going abroad so um we say travel safe
and you say you intend to listen to the
I you know in your room that's very good
you should do that um now before that
you know are you allowed to meditate on
God sure you are you know you want to go
out to the Sun s Under the Sun and be on
the beach you know sometime they have
those beaches rocking with music and you
know carrying on and if you still
keeping the Sabbath day sometimes your
room is the best place to keep the
Sabbath day at So based on what's really
going on at the beach out there you know
be careful make sure you you know with
somebody or with people but um sometime
the room is the best place to keep it
cuz sometime they partying and music and
Mar reader and down but um let's go into
um Psalms 1 Psalms 1 and one we already
read about uh you know the Sabbath day
being holy and the Lord tell us to keep
it you know holy unto him
so uh Psalms
1 and
one because you mentioned meditating
which is also a good thing read one and
two brother blessed is is the man that
walketh not in the counsel of the
ungodly or nor standeth in the way of
Sinners nor sth in the seat of the
scornful but his Delight is in the law
of the Lord and in his law doeth he
meditate day and night which is good
advice all the time but on that Sabbath
day you want to make sure that you just
you know have your place where that you
can reserve and just be with the Lord
and give him all of your time on that
day anybody
else all right hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next one
moving on she also ask how did the
dinosaurs and all those hu all those
large creatures become destroyed or
extinct as they were not around Way
Before the
Flood all right guess caller this
question about the dinosaur was and you
know they want to know you know were
they around not around Way Before the
Flood guess
called yeah well the the the scriptures
itself let you know how the Lord
destroyed all of them because that's the
way he destroyed the people in Noah's
day let's
go let's go he drowned them let's go
into Genesis the first chapter we going
to read
one through uh 2 then we're going to
skip down and read 6
through1 okay Genesis 1 1 and 2
first in the beginning God created the
Heaven and the Earth and the Earth was
without form and void and darkness was
upon the face of the deep and the spirit
of God moved upon the face of the
waters now that let you know in the
beginning was God created the Heaven and
Earth but the spirit of God moved up on
the face of the deep you know and and uh
uh uh and the spirit of God moved upon
the face of the waters that mean that
heaven and the Earth was there but the
only thing that was exposed was the
water SK down to verse n and
continue and God said let the waters
under the heaven be gathered together
under one place and let the dry land
appear and it was so and God called the
dry land Earth and the Gathering
Together of the waters called he seas
and God saw that it was
good now so the whole thing is the water
the the the Earth and everything was
under the
water and everything in that uh uh uh
oner was still there in the ground so
just like he uh destroyed the water
drown the people in Noah's day he
drowned the
dinosaurs and to let you know that the
Dinos dinosaurs wouldn't there when new
will come across go to Genesis 6 and
read verse
19 Genesis 6 and9 says and of every
living thing of All Flesh two of every
sort shall shalt thou bring into the ark
to keep them alive with thee they shall
be male and
female and it is unclean two of All
Flesh and mean all animals now go to
Genesis 7 and
two of every clean Beast Thou shalt take
to thee by sevens the male and the
female and of Beast that are not clean
by two the male and the
female now it let you know that God
intended to bring every
animal on the ark with Noah to make sure
he would not leave one animal or one
bird over there so that mean that the
dinosaurs was not in Adam's creation
they was before the creation but they
got drowned just like the old world got
drowned that's why the Lord made this
statement to uh Noah let's go to Genesis
9 and read verse
one Genesis 9 and verse one says and God
blessed Noah and his sons and said unto
them be fruitful and multiply and
replenish the Earth that mean to
repopulate the Earth so now they came
across when he said
replenish that mean that the Earth was
replenished before when during the
dinosaur and the dinosaurs could not
have been in Noah's creation or they
would still be here because God took
time to bring every Beast across the
flood so how did the Lord destroy them
same way he destroyed the world in
Noah's day he drowned
them that's all I have to say all right
hope that ansed your question as we move
on to our next question next one Mr
lesan and Linda Perry asks are we able
to eat
Hala uh fit to eat or use According to
Islamic law meat beef bacon or
lamb brother Dre what you
say we don't we don't uh deal with Halal
in that way Hal is a the Muslim way of
their dietary law and and what they deal
with and kosher is similar the the
process in which they go about to
slaughter
animals what we did and and in halal
rabbit is is okay to eat shrimp and all
kind of other things are okay to eat but
we don't eat those things so we deal
with Leviticus l leus 11 let's just look
at a couple of things there Leviticus 11
and pick it up at verse
6 start started uh one start at one
Leviticus 11 and one and the Lord spake
unto Moses and to Aaron saying unto them
speak unto the children of Israel saying
these are the Beast which ye shall eat
among all the beasts that are on the
earth so what's
go ahead go ahead whatsoever parteth the
hoof and is clovenfooted and cheth the
cud among the Beast that shall ye eat
now this is one of the things that
people that are Muslims eat that we
don't eat verse six go ahead and the
hair because he cheth the cud but
divideth not the hoof he is unclean to
you so they eat that but it is unclean
to us now
skip down to verse n read n and 10 and
that'll be
it these shall ye eat of all that are in
the water whatsoever hath fins and
scales in the waters in the seas and in
the rivers them shall ye eat and all
that have not fins and scales in the
seas and in the rivers of all that move
in the
waters and of any living thing which is
in the water
they shall be an Abomination unto you
that's right so we don't eat those
things now and the Muslims that eat Hal
they eat shrimp and and other things and
they they still considered halow under
their Islamic
law but we don't so we go by Leviticus
11 and and I hope that that helps in
terms of their slaughtering system they
lit the throat and and drain out all of
the blood of the animals so do those
that do kosher so that's the process of
uh make making something
halow I hope that helped all right
brother good light and little that
Deuteronomy 142 also talks about what we
can eat and can't eat yes sir but thank
you for that brother hope that answered
their question sister Deborah time check
yes the time is is
8:47 uh Malik Shure uh
asked could you explain John 8 verse
41 some say verse some say this verse
means that Joseph and Mary had relations
before marriage and Joseph is his
father okay let's go to to John 8 and 41
and uh since it's now
8:48 Let's uh open the remainder of the
questions to the panel until it's time
for the show to come to an end John
8 and uh verse 41 and before you read
that again brother sister Deborah what
was the question again the question is
from this scripture he states that some
says that Joseph and Mary had relations
before marriage and Joseph is his
father read John 841 and let's open it
up to the
panel ye do the Deeds of your father
then said they to him we be we be not
born of fornication we have one father
even
God all right Pharisees were uh the
Pharisees didn't believe that Jesus uh
came forth of a virgin birth they didn't
believe that you know but Mary Said by
her own mouth she had not known a man um
before Jesus came okay so let's go to
Luke the first
chapter and read verse 3
4 Luke 1 and 34
yeah pick it up at the 31 actually read
31-34 Luke
31-34 and behold Thou shalt conceive in
thy womb and bring forth a son and shalt
call his name Jesus he shall be great
and shall be called the son of the
highest and the Lord God shall give unto
him the Throne of his father David and
he shall reign over the house of Jacob
forever and of his kingdom there shall
be no end
then said Mary unto the angel how shall
this be seeing I know not a man okay you
go and it's written so we believe the
word of God that's all I got on it and
you could read the same thing in Matthew
uh the 1 chapter verses 24-2 James okay
M get back off of what uh you know we
got two two witnesses here Matthew 20
Matthew 1 read verse
24-25 okay then Joseph being raised from
sleep did as the angel of the Lord had
bitten him and took unto him his wife
and he and knew her not till she had
brought forth her firstborn son and he
called his name Jesus there you
go yep knew her
not yeah all right so we hope that ansed
your question as we move on to our next
one where time is ticking yes next
question Zion has two questions his
first one uh is who are the tears in
Matthew 13 verse 38 and also in Matthew
19 okay Matthew 13 verse 38 then his
other question is in Matthew 19 verse1
17 why did Jesus say there is none good
but one that is God wasn't Jesus perfect
also all right let's go to the first one
was Matthew 13 right yes Matthew 13
verse 38 they want to know Zion want to
know who are the
tear all right so don't we go and read
that and then we'll open it up to the
panel
because this was Jesus here breaking
down a parable pick it up at 37 read
down they want to know who were the
tears the tears were the ones that came
up short go ahead the children of the
Wicked on serving Satan but go ahead
verse uh 3 37 brother he answered and
said sorry pick it up at 36 read 36 y
Matthew 13 verse 36 then Jesus sent the
multitude away and went into the house
and his disciples came came unto him
saying declare unto us the parable of
the tears of the field he answered and
said unto them he that sth the good seed
is the son of man the field is the world
the good seed are the children of the
Kingdom but the tears are the children
of the wicked one the law Breakers the
ones that serving Satan yeah there's the
answer right there y yeah every read 39
to about
the the enemy that sth them is the devil
the Harvest is the end of the world and
the reapers are the Angels and if you
tear what happens in 40 as therefore the
tears are gathered and burned in the
fire so shall it be in the end of this
world so you don't want to be no tear
right Dre that's right
all right now that second question in
Matthew second question yes is Matthew
19 verse
17 why did Jesus
say uh there is none good but one that
is God wasn't Jesus perfect
Also let's go and read that let's pick
it up um at that verse 16 and read that
16 and
17 okay Matthew 9 : 16-1 17 says and
behold one came and said unto him good
Master what good thing shall I do that I
may have eternal life and he said unto
him why callest thou me good there is
none good but one that is God but if
thou will enter into life keep the
Commandments all right there's none good
but one that is God yes caller
that's one you going to have to ask
Jesus when you're
see all right we're gonna move on to our
next question all right uh the next
question Miss Wade uh uh
asked what nationality was Father
Abraham what
nationality with Father Abraham panel
the HEB
Hebrew yes
sir I think
14 where is it brother Jerome I believe
it's Genesis
14 yeah uh Genesis 14 and 13 yeah read
12 through U 13 okay Genesis 14: 12 and
13 say and they took lot Abram's
brother's son who dwelt in Sodom and his
goods and departed and there came one
that had escaped and told Abram the
Hebrew for he dwelt in the plain of mry
the Amorite brother esol the brother of
Anor and these were Confederate with
Abram yes
sir all right moving on to our next
question because we know he was Hebrew
of Hebrews go ahead yes uh Miss Love
most love ask for you to
explain Matthew 18 versus 8 and nine
does that literally mean to cut off your
limbs or just to stop what you're
doing let's go to Matthew
18 I'm
there and read that verse 8 and N we go
open up to the panel and that second
half was correct yeah you can stop doing
it you should read wherefore If thy hand
or thy foot offend thee cut them off and
cast them from thee it is better for
thee to enter into life halt or maimed
rather than having two hands or two feet
to be cast into Everlasting fire yeah
and if
thine read saying you stop doing it
because if you get into the kingdom
you're not going to have one arm missing
or one eye missing that's right you're
going to be
perfect yep that merely mean like she
said just stop doing what you're doing
wrong that's right cut it
out all
right moving on to our next one yes
moving on Christy Watson uh
ask when we become
God will we know whether our mother
father sister or brother who didn't make
the first
resurrection will we be sad will we show
some kind of
emotion open to the panel I know um you
will be extremely happy you made it open
to the
panel I don't know
yep so we are we're going to move on as
time is ticking look like we down to our
last question or two sister Deborah next
yes next one Valencia asks what does it
mean to eat upon the
mountains and Ezekiel
18 verse 6 and verse 15 is
given Ezekiel 18 what verse
6 and verse 15 all right Why Don't We Go
There Brother James Ezekiel
18 I'm
there and
um why don't you pick it up at that
verse five because um if you be just and
do that which is lawful and right and
have not eaten upon the mountains so it
must be something bad about that eating
upon the mountains but read five six go
ahead but if a man be just and do that
which is lawful and right and have not
eaten upon the mountains neither hath
lifted up his eyes to the idols of the
House of Israel neither hath defiled his
neighbors's wife neither has come near
to a menstruous woman all right open to
the
pan J to verse
15 yeah all right let's read 15 that not
eaten upon the mountains neither ha
lifted up his eyes to the idols of the
House of Israel hath not defiled his
neighbor's
wife
yeah open to the pan they want guess go
Israel they used to they used to worship
P Gods on the highest hill they can find
yeah that's what he's talking
about yeah so if if you have not done
that then hey and be just and lawful
then ye shall
live that's it all right uh sister
Deborah one more question and we have
come to an end okay and this one is
interesting here uh M short Cas
strawberry um ask is God the father's
name
Jesus is God the father's name Jesus
well we know that is the name above
every name open to the pth yes it
is you in the scripture where he said he
gave him in in in uh uh
Philippians I think it's the second
chapter in verse 5
yeah I read now uhuh Philippians yeah um
Philippians 2
uh I think it comes in around at verse 9
let's go to Philippians 2
okay Philippians 2 and you want me to
start at verse
n
um yeah yeah verse nine brother okay
wherefore God Al also hath highly
exalted him and given him a name which
is above every name that at the name of
Jesus every KNE should bow of things in
heaven and things in Earth and things
under the Earth and that every
tongue should confess that Jesus Christ
is Lord to the glory of God the Father
yes
call now it it said so he gave a name
above every name because he gave his own
name let's go into St John the 5th
chapter
where say I come in my father's
name yeah St John
5 see that's verse 43 yeah 43 directly
St John 5:43 says I am come in my
father's name and you receive me not if
another shall come in his own name him
you will
receive so now John the Baptist came in
the spirit of Elijah but he came in his
own name but Jesus came in his father's
name now what was jesus' name let's go
into Exodus the 6th chapter before he
came in his father's
name Exodus the 6
chapter okay Exodus
6 start verse
two Exodus 6 verse2 says and God spake
unto Moses
and said unto him I am the Lord and I
appeared unto Abraham unto Isaac and
unto Jacob by the name of God Almighty
but by my name Jehovah was I not known
to
them was so that was Jesus name before
he came in the flesh
Jehovah when he came in
theh he came in his father's name so
yeah the father's name is Jesus
all
right all right we hope that answered
your question with a good question and
our session on tonight i' like to thank
everybody from all around the world who
tuned in with us but if you submitted a
question and we didn't have a chance to
get to it please don't resubmit us
sister to Deborah take it put it in
rotation and we'll deal with that next
Wednesday so we want to thank you all
once again for viewing with us and until
we come together again be safe be
blessed
stay prayerful and may the Lord have
mercy on us all close us out brother
James Our Father which are is which art
in heaven Hallowed be thy name thy
kingdom come thy will be done in earth
as it is in heaven give us this day our
daily bread and forgive us our debts as
we forgive our Deb TOs and lead us not
into temptation but Deliver Us from Evil
for th thine is the kingdom and the
power and the glory forever in Jesus
name we pray